[{"id":1,"question":"Which ad component has three fields that allow 30 characters each?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"the headline","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"the description","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"the website URL","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"the call-to-action","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":2,"question":"When reviewing the **Recommendations** page, you identify a suggestion that you want to use. What is the most practical way to implement the suggestion?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Copy the optimization, visit the ad group, and past the optimization.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Follow the step-by-step instructions.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Visit the ad group, click the **Optimization** drop-down, and select **Apply All**.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Click **Apply** on the recommendation.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":3,"question":"Griff has noticed that his best-performing keywords has started to see an increased CPC, despite no changes on his part. What is the most likely reason for this?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"ad Quality Score increase","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"reduction of landing page inbound links","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"reduction in daily budget","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"increased competition","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":4,"question":"You are running a campaign that will consist of 15 ads. What is the minimum number of ad groups that you can have as part of the campaign?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"1","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"5","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"3","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"15","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":5,"question":"Braxton has his maximum bid set to $","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"$3.96","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"$3.95","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"$4","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"$5","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":6,"question":"Maurice creates an ad headline that reads \"Buy **{Keyword:hats}** Today\". Which headline could `not` be displayed to a user for this ad?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Buy Caps Today","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Buy Helmets Today","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Buy Fedoras Today","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Buy Hats","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":7,"question":"Which choice is `not` an option when configuring `ad` extensions?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"product extensions","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"sitelink extensions","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"message extensions","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"callout extensions","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":8,"question":"Which choice is a best practice when designing a landing page for an ad campaign?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"having lots of inbound links","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"using JavaScript","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"relevant content matching the ad","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"enrolling in Ad Central","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":9,"question":"Which choice has no impact on Quality Score?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"ad relevance","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"expected clickthrough rate","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"landing page experience","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"max CPC bid","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":10,"question":"Marcelina wants to know how many sales her Google Ads brought in. What should she set up?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"target CPA bidding","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"conversion tracking","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"custom deep links","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"custom display URLs","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":11,"question":"Kellan creates an ad headline that reads \"Buy **{Keyword:Shoes}** Today\". What is this an example ad?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"automatic headline replacement","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"keyword insertion","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"dynamic bidding","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"auto replacement","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":12,"question":"Which factor does Google Ads consider when determining whether a remarketing list qualifies for a similar audiences list?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"the number of visitors on the list","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"the amount of revenue generated by the list","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"the average bid targeting the list","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"the average monthly spend targeting the list","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":13,"question":"An auction has a normal bid of $.50 but there is an active bid adjustment of -20%. What is the final bid amount?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"$0.40","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"$0.60","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"$0.04","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"$0.06","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":14,"question":"Raisa starting running a new ad campaign a month ago. Without making any changes, she noticed that her CPC has gone down significantly in the last week. What could have caused this?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"a decrease in ad Quality Score","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"an increase in daily budget","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"changes in competitor campaigns","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"an increase of landing page inbound links","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":15,"question":"Which ad rotation setting uses machine learning to prioritize ads based upon expected performance?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Rotate evenly","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Optimize","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Manual rotation","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Rotate indefinitely","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":16,"question":"Clara is running retargeted display ads, but does not want her audience to experience ad fatique. What should be configure?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"ad scheduling","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"a frequency cap","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"an impression cap","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"auto ad rotation","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":17,"question":"If someone performs a search for \"most comfortable chair\", which ad description text would likely perform the best?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Don't be uncomfortable. Get a new chair. Try the LumbarPro today.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Experience the most comfortable chair, with more than 1,000 five-star reviews.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Try the LumbarPro, a chair that has been reviewed as comfortable by more than 1,000 people.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Need a new chair? The LumbarPro is the highest rated chair. Try this chair, today.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":18,"question":"Why would you use callout extensions?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"to share pricing on various business offerings","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"to highlight key features and unique offers","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"to show reviews of your product or service","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"to add phone numbers to the ad","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":19,"question":"You have a maximum CPC bid of $4 for the keyword **Coffee Mugs**. What tool could you use to determine the projected result of raising the bid to $4.50?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"CPC Optimizer","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Bid Simulator","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Google Analytics","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Lighthouse","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":20,"question":"Which keyword status is not valid?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Geographically restricted","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Under review","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Paused","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Eligible","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":21,"question":"When reviewing a campaign, you notice that your cost per conversion on desktop is much lower than on mobile. How should you optimize the bidding strategy is you wanted to increase the overall number of campaign conversions?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Increase the desktop bid adjustment for this campaign","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Increase the ad frequency for the campaign","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Decrease the desktop bid adjustment for the campaign","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Increase both the desktop and mobile ad adjustments","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":22,"question":"With Google's Active View technology, when is an impression of a display ad considered viewable?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"when the user leaves the page the ad appears on","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"when any part of the ad is on-screen for 5 seconds","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"when the entire ad first appears on the screen","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"when at least 50% of the ad is on-screen for at least 1 second","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":23,"question":"Rhama wants to increase her bids for any customers that are within a selected radius of her storefront. What would you recommend she do?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Create a location bid adjustment","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Use automated bidding","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Create an ad group with higher bids, targeted to that geographical region","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Restrict the campaign to only the radius","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":24,"question":"The standard approach to submitting product data to Google Ads is through the use of a product **_**.","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"link","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"ad","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"feed","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"extension","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":25,"question":"In order to create a similat audience, you must provide Google Ads with **_**.","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"a budget","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"a tracking pixel","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"all of these answers","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"a seed list of users","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":26,"question":"How do responsive search ads increase your likelihood of reaching more customers?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"They provide multiple headline and description options, so ads automatically evolve based on performance.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Responsive search ads are mobile optimized","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"All of these answers","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Responsive reach ads receive preferential treatment in the google ads auction","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":27,"question":"Sion is having a sale that will last three days. He wants his ad text to show how much time is remaining in the sale. Would would you recoment for Sion?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Use the sale extension and set the sale duration for each time zone.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Do not include the sale in the ad text, as this likley violated Google Ads editorial policies.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Add a countdown customizer to the ad text.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Manually adjust the ad text as frequently as possible to reflect the time remaining","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":28,"question":"Tabitha has a mobile application that is complementary to her website. She wants to make it known to potential customers, but driving app downloads is not her main goal. What would you recommend she configure on her Google Ads?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"app extension","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Universal App campaign","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Mobile App campaign","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"download extension","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":29,"question":"Which solution allows you to show ads in Google search results, only if the user has previously visited your website?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"MDC","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"ECPC","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"RLSA","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Target ROAS","answer":false,"code":false}]}]